<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Abacha Music]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Abacha Music]]></description>
        <link>http://abachamusic.com.au/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 01:59:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://abachamusic.com.au/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 01:59:57 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Music Lessons]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Music Lessons</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/bf0c77c9-6bc8-4af3-bad2-0aaa5f000db1.jpg">,<p>I cater to teaching students of any age at my private studio in Eleebana. Whether you’re a beginner or an expert, I would be more than happy to work with you to learn the basics or improve your technique.</p>,<p>Specialising in teaching the <a href="https://www.ameb.edu.au/">Australian Musical Examinations Board</a> syllabus (AMEB) and <a href="https://www.ameb.edu.au/music-craft">Music Craft</a> theory programme allows me to provide an individually tailored music programme whilst also giving you the opportunity to complete examinations with one of the most respected bodies in the field.</p>,<p>For the younger students, my Music Theory is Fun series helps to grow the understanding of musical theory from the beginning of the music learning process whilst remaining fun and entertaining.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://abachamusic.com.au/private-music-lessons/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0a0f5246-43bf-4cf3-a8ca-5c4cc15c36cc</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 13:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Me]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>About Me</h1>,<h2>Music Teacher and Author</h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/fe580d8c-75e2-410d-9944-9e1b0078d754.jpg">,<p>I bring over 35 years of teaching experience to the art of piano, flute, and music theory and trains students of all ages in the Newcastle and Hunter region. I currently teach at the following locations:</p>,<ul><li>Piano and Music Theory at The University of Newcastle’s Faculty of Music</li><li>Piano and Music Theory at several K-12 schools</li><li>Piano, Flute and Music Theory at my private studio in Eleebana</li></ul>,<p>I studied at the Newcastle Conservatorium of Music, where I completed my Certificate of Music Teaching in 1981. Continuing my studies, I was awarded the Diploma of the State Conservatorium of Music in 1982 and completed my Bachelor of Arts (Musicology) at the University of New England during 1989. I undertook Music Technology at The University of Newcastle in 1995 and completed my Masters Degree through research in 2003.</p>,<p>I am also the author of the <em>Music Theory is Fun</em> book series and the <em>Musical Instruments</em> school textbook which caters for years 7-8 classes.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://abachamusic.com.au/about-me/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9f2b83d8-deac-4f50-8af3-f5bbe88eac6b</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 07:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contact and Location]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Contact and Location</h1>,<p>Feel free to get in touch with me by phone, email, or sms. If I am with a student I may not be able to answer your call and will get back to you as soon as possible.</p>,<p>Call or SMS: 0413 150 188<br>Email: info@abachamusic.com.au</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-location/?latitude=-32.993929&longitude=151.652607&zoom=16&address=6%20Wollundry%20Close%2C%20Eleebana%2C%20New%20South%20Wales%202282%2C%20Australia"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>http://abachamusic.com.au/contact-and-location/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c86f05ed-135a-4531-9d57-4afb505479b4</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 13:36:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>